<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Christa Clark]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Christa Clark]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/christa-clark/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 18:12:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/christa-clark/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Four</h1><h2>Fox Mulder</h2><p></p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/christa-clark/four/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e870d9d9-0a48-4cf6-be2a-b7801eb915e5</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 18:12:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Two</h1><h2>Terrible Twos</h2><p>Most claim this to be a time of terror, but this pertains to new parents. I was a princess, I was treated like East Texas Royalty. My grandmother was running for Houston City Council and would tote me around the campaign trail. I was pretty cute, and my best friend was a Dog named Max and the bayou we lived next to. That year was hard for me. I moved to Austin, away from my beloved Grandma and Max, and my sister was born, an event I was entirely unprepared for. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/christa-clark/two/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4cd092d4-fd15-448e-bea5-cf1778e9b297</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 18:10:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Three</h1><h2>Illumination</h2><p>When I was three, every night I would dream that I walked around my home, late at night, opening doors until I found these gorgeous humanoids comprised solely of white light. They would speak to me softly and instill hope in my small self. Then, my sister was born and life as I knew it came to an end. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/christa-clark/three/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ba73cae4-adaf-47a7-8702-277b9e7e9878</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 18:10:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>One</h1><h2>Tabula Rasa</h2><p>An absence of preconceived ideas or predetermined goals; a clean slate, is exactly what I was given when my tiny body was born into this world. I remember nothing, but I know I was, if only for a brief moment, whole, complete, and perfect. We start out that way and then seem to spend our adult lives trying to get back to that space of mind overflowing with purity and bliss. Teddy, aka my earthly, akashic record was my best friend. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/christa-clark/one/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b48e1f18-1cbe-44c0-8bd9-c0e7f33203b0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 18:09:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Born ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Born </h1><p>I was born at 7:30 PM, in Houston, Texas, on January 13th, 1994. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/christa-clark/born/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">88cdc7ec-9964-408f-a691-02e76ee55460</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 18:07:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Christa's love story with the tech industry began while teaching financial literacy to kids after school, and conceptualizing an app to drive home this topic in everyday life. From there Christa built her brainchild: Heartworthy Co., a web design agency with the mission of rescuing professionals from outdated websites and poor user experiences. In this next chapter, she is now lead UX/UI designer for Skunkworx Lab. Responsive web design is her religion, and in her spare time spread the good word of Code to willing converts.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/christa-clark/christas-love-story-with-the-tech-industry-began-while-teac/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5c470a1c-47ca-4587-946c-d50180b3d56f</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 15:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>